fbcash.com 2011-12-31

# 

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or fill out a form.  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or mailing address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

**To improve our website**  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

**To process transactions**  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

**To send periodic emails**  
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

**How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.

**Do we use cookies?**  
Yes, we use cookies for non-malicious purposes. We use cookies to help us serve to you the most appropriate pages that would be useful to you. We also use cookies to determine where sales have originated from.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  
**  
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  
**  
Terms and Conditions**  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://fbcash.com/privacy-policy/

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://FBcash.com

support@FBcash.com
